All right, we're going to speedrun this
a little bit. So, I'm going to show you
how to find the minimum, the maximum,
and the absolute value. So, all of these
are in the math library. So, just like
we accessed um the math library in the
last video, we'll access in this video
by doing capital M atth math dot. And in
this case, to find the minimum, you do
math.min. Um you'll notice it's that
cube shape again. So, that means we're
going to use parenthesis. Um, and now it
says that we need to give it a bunch of
values. So if I type 5 47 91
and I alert that,
we save it and we go to our web browser.
It says that the minimum value in that
list of numbers that I gave it was a
one. Um, if we change this to math.max
and save it and go back over, maximum
number I typed was nine. Um,
so that's how min and max work. Um,
we'll also alert an absolute value.
Absolute value is just something's
distance from zero. So like -2 is two
steps from zero. So that's the absolute
value of -2 is two. So um, we'll take
math.abs ABS is how you do absolute
value. If you put parenthesis, it needs
a number. So, I'm going to give it a
negative -2 and I'm going to alert that.
We save it. We come over and we reload
our page. We get two exactly like we
expected. So, um if you are wondering
about how to use math functions, um I'd
recommend again checking W3 Schools. It
has a whole outline of a whole bunch of
different math functions and information
on how to use them. These are the ones
we'll use in this course. Um, and then
the one that I'll cover in the next
video, which is how to generate a random
nublet.